discoverourtown.com 2013-06-10

# DiscoverOurTown Privacy Policy

**DiscoverOurTown Privacy Policy**

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.yahoo.com&sealid=101%20)DiscoverOurTown takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how DOT treats personal information that DOT collects and receives, including information related to your past use of DOT products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DOT does not own or control, or to people that DOT does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

      **  
General**

  * DOT collects personal information when you register with DOT, when you use DOT�s services, when you visit DOT pages or the pages of certain DOT partners. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with DOT and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * DOT collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 
  * DOT automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, DOT information, and the page you request. 
  * DOT uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

      **Children**

  * DOT will not contact children under age 18 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. 
  * DOT does not ask a child under age 17 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * DOT does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with DOT under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help DOT communicate with you about offers from DOT and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of DOT�s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if DOT is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, DOT will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * DOT displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
    * DOT does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
    * DOT�s advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 
  * DOT works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 
  * DOT uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on our Web site, other Web sites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>.  

**Cookies**

  * DOT may set and access DOT�s cookies on your computer. 
  * DOT lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to DOT�s cookies. 
  * DOT uses web beacons to access DOT�s cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with DOT�s products and services. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 
  * To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * DOT may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your DOT account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * DOT is trustcertified and the certification applies to all English-language sites under the DiscoverOurTown.com� domain. If you feel that your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php), an independent privacy organization. TRUSTe serves as a liaison with DOT to resolve your concern. 
  * If you have questions or suggestions, please send your comments to [info@DiscoverOurTown.com](mailto:info@DiscoverOurTown.com)� you can contact us at: 

DiscoverOurTown.com, Inc.

535 Port Terminal Circle

Vicksburg, MS�  39183

601-636-4404

Info@DiscoverOurTown.com

�
